EDWIN AU

WEB DEVELOPER | GRAPHIC DESIGNER

https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing

https://www.linkedin.com/in/eaudesign



416-880-3791



PROFILE As a creative web developer with experience in graphic design and product design, I'm passionate about creating modern and intuitive applications that put user experience at the forefront. Feel free to reach out and find how my rigorous HTML, CSS and JavaScript skillset combined with my focus in layouts, colours and typography can benefit your team.

EDUCATION



Web Development Program

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

> Full Stack Web Immersive

> JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS3, ¡Query, AJAX, SQL, SASS, HAML, Sketch

Ryerson University

B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

Sep 1998 - April 2002

> Product design, graphic design, marketing, trend analysis.

> Presentation & communication skills. Research & Development focus.

Central Saint Martins (UK)

Experimentation Design Course

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001

> Selected by Ryerson University to partake in this foreign exchange program.

> Thesis: Triple bottom line & green design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RendezYou

Web Developer | Graphic Designer @ Mar 2017 - Present

https://rendezyou.herokuapp.com

- > Responsive design across all browser platforms; Full-stack CRUD development.
- > Built on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Adobe CS6, Ruby, Rails, jQuery, SQL.

Thinkway Toys

Design Manager @ Mar 2016 - Mar 2017

www.thinkwaytoys.com

- > Design Manager in licensed hardlines products Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign:
 - Lucas Films | Star Wars Rogue One
 - Disney/Pixar | Cars 3
 - Universal Studios | Despicable Me 3

Disney Consumer Products

Product Developer ② Nov 2013 - Mar 2016

www.disneyconsumerproducts.com

- > Provided creative leadership in the design and development of Disney Branded Consumer Products sold across Canada.
- > One of five designers working out of Disney Canada's head office. Guiding 50+ licensees on product design ranging from apparel and home accessories, to toys and arts & crafts. These products were widely sold at Walmart Canada, Target Canada, Dollarama, Canadian Tire and Toys R Us.
- > Work days range from managing online product design approvals, to traveling and meeting with vendors communicating Disney design goals and initiatives.

Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy)

Associate, Graphic Designer ② Sep 2012 - Sep 2013

- > Having accumulated 10 years (full profile on Linkedin) of product development experience in Toronto - I decided to take my skills as a designer abroad, resulting with the opportunity to work at Dolce & Gabbana's head quarters in Italy Milan for a year, helping their design and sales team with preparation and sales of their Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 collections.
- > Created Fall 2013 sales deck and Spring 2014 training material.

▶ National Bank Financial

Desktop Publisher, Graphic Designer ② Dec 2010 - Dec 2011

- > Desktop Publisher with Graphic Design experience at NBF Institutional Equities.
- > Fast paced and tight knit environment. Duties include formatting and publishing business documents in print and online, designing corporate invites and banners.
- > Publishing Daily Notes onto www.nbcn.ca, as well as onto other financial portals including Bloomberg, Capital IQ, TheMarkets.com, Reuters, FactSet.

SKILLS





Sketch







































